Guide to the Committee on the Protection of Human Subjects, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1967-1983; Accession 1988-A-083
  - Zigler: Cognition and Motivation in Retarded Individuals, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 477)
  - Fowler: The Development of Memory in Reading, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 478)
  - Tetlock: Influence of Impression Management Goals on Attributions, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 479)
  - London: Insomnia Assessment Questionnaire, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 480)
  - Brenes: Women and Depression: A Study on the Sex Biases in Diagnosis, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 481)
  - Reiss, Jr.: Social Science Research Training: Sociology of Social Control, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 482)
  - Pike: The Baking of Police Officers: The Social Organization of the Police Academy, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 483)
  - Berman: Coping with Interpersonal Loss: Adjustment in Divorced and Widowed Woman, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 484)
  - Scarr: Graduate Research Training in Child Psychology, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 485)
  - Walker: An Experimental Investigation of Non-decisionmaking, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 486)
  - Pospisil: Acculturation, Urbanization, and Law, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 487)
  - London: The effects of attentional vs. directional instructions in biofeedback control of heart rate, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 488)
  - Singer: Clinical-Community Psychology Training Program, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 489)
  - Kessen: Temporal Aspects of Visual Perception in the Very Young Infant, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 490)
  - Furrow: Social and Asocial Speech in Language-Learning Children, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 491)
  - Veilleux: Self-Image Disparity as a Function of Premorbid Social Competence and Psychiatric Diagnosis, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 492)
  - Klos: The Effects of Confrontation Style and Outcome on Subsequent Thought: A Simulation of Parent-Adolescent Interaction, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 493)
  - Cascione: Development of Adaptive Behavior in Retarded Persons, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 494)
  - Zigler: Cognition and Motivation in Retarded Individuals, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 495)
  - Fowler: The Development of Memory in Reading, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 496)
  - Tetlock: Influence of Impression Efanagement Goals on Attributions, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 497)
  - London: Insomnia Assessment Questionnaire, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 498)
  - Brenes: Women and Depression: A Study on the Sex Biases in Diagnosis, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 499)
  - Reiss, Jr.: Social Science Research Training: Sociology of Social Control, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 500)
  - Pike: The Baking of Police Officers: The Social Organization of the Police Academy, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 501)
  - Janis and Abelson: Program in Personality and Social Psychology, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 502)
  - Caparule: Effects of Educational Mainstreaming on Probability Learning, Imitation and Self-concept, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 503)
  - Heller: Developmental Changes in Prediction on Another's Behavior Based on Dispositional Attributions, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 504)
  - Fridlund: Classification of Affectfve State Using Facial EMG Activity, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 505)
  - Pescosolido: Nation-wide Survey of Coroners, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 506)
  - Reiss: Social Sciences Research Training: The Sociology of Social Control, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 507)
  - Berndt: Decision-Making in Children's Peer Groups, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 508)
  - Yee: A Study of Young People's Ratings of Their Real, Ideal, and Social Self-Images in Skill Areas of Self-Reported Interest, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 509)
  - Rennert: Choice, Expectancy and Information, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 510)
  - Kubovy: Reading Connected Text with Rapid Sequential Visual Presentation, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 511)
  - Healy: Process Models of Probabilistic Categorization Decisions, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 512)
  - Scarr and Sternberg: Transmission of the Components of Intelligence and Social Cognition, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 513)
  - Repetti: Children's Imagination, Sex Role Attitudes, and Television-Viewing Patterns, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 514)
  - Berndt: Friendships and Social Interactions: Relationships of Retarded Children with Retarded and Non-Retarded Peers, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 515)
  - Rhodes: Differential Control of Heart Rate and Pulse Transit Time Through Biofeedback Training, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 516)
  - Tower: Adjective Checklist Development, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 517)
  - Heilman: Reducing Occupational Sex Bias: Some Structural Solutions to Attitudinal Problems, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 518)
  - Rodin: Institutionalization of the Aged: Stressors and Coping, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 519)
  - Weaver: Evaluation of Film under "Media Design for Handicapped" Project, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 520)
  - Wheator: Interaction Models for Selected Psychiatric Disorders, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 521)
  - Moore: Prosocial Development in Second and Fifth Grades, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 522)
  - Garner: Perception of Structure, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 523)
  - Tower: Parents 'Preferences and Preschoolers' Behaviors, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 524)
  - Ahern: Differential Lateralization for Positive versus Negative Emotion in the Human Brain: EEG Power Spectral Analysis, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 525)
  - Cuba: Urban Life on the Frontier, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 526)
  - Myers: The Epidemiology Catchment Area Program, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 527)
  - Feldman: Elements of Word Perception, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 528)
  - Crowder: The Processing of Speech in Human Short-Term Memory, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 529)
  - Alderfer: Method and Theory on Intergroups in Organizations, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 530)
  - Zigler: Immediate and Long-Term Effects of Interventions for Children at Risk, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 531)
  - Christoph: A Comparison of Coping Imagery and Positive Imagery in the Desensitization Treatment of Phobias, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 532)
  - Fetter: Development of Diagnosis Related Groups Using ICD-9-CM Codes, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 533)
  - Scarr: Bermuda Evaluation Project, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 534)
  - Mogenstern: Possible Cardiovascular Effects of Vasectomy in Man, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 535)
  - Schwartz: Biofeedback, Facial Response Patterning and Emotion, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 536)
  - Scarr: Family Determinants of Educational and Occupational Choices, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 537)
  - Diaz: Preadolescent Friendships, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 538)
  - Feldman, et al.: Face Recognition as a Function of Judged Similarity, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 539)
  - Weaver: We All Have Tales, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 540)
  - Peters: Funeral Decision Making and Bereavement, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 541)
  - Kubovy: Attention and Pre-Attention in Audition and Vision, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 542)
  - Kubovy: Attention and Pre-Attention in Audition and Vision, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 543)
  - Gianno: Resin Technology and Trade in Ancient and Modem Penisular Malaysia, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 544)
  - Healy: The Size and the Nature of Reading Units, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 545)
  - Sherwood: Maliseet-Passamaquoddy Inflectional Morphology and Syntax, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 546)
  - Singer: Clinical Psychology: Health and Child/Community, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 547)
  - Diaz: Preadolescent Friendships, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 548)
  - Roseman: Perception of Biographical Events, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 549)
  - Kessen: Temporal Aspects of Young Infants' Visual Perception, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 550)
  - Piotrkowski: Work and the Mental Health of Families, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 551)
  - Anthony: The Role of Imagery in Physiological Self -Control, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 552)
  - Black: Sotry Underst anding, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 553)
  - Piotrkowski: Children's Attitudes Toward Parental Work Roles, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 554)
  - Shwartz: Visual Information Processing, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 555)
  - Schorr: The Chaining of Actions in Determining Outcomes, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 556)
  - Cascione: Development of Adaptive Behavior in Retarded Persons, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 557)
  - Barton: Health Attitudes, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 558)
  - Romo: Social Networks and Treatment in Psychiatric Institutions, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 559)
  - Black and Doob: Consumer Analysis in Support of Innovative (Utility) Rate Policy, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 560)
  - Chin: Time Manipulation in Ego and Attribution Theory, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 561)
  - Schwartz: Personality and Blood Pressure in College Students, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 562)
  - Hakuta: Acquisition of English by Adult Working Class Native Speakers of Spanish, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 563)
  - Kristeller: Eating Patterns Questionnaire Research, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 564)
  - Resnick: Child Custody Decision-Making, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 565)
  - Singer: Effects of Experimentally-Induced Waking Dreams on Creative Problem Solving, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 566)
  - Schwab: Effects of Stress on Hemispheric Asymmetry and Heart Rate to Approach and Avoidance Emotions, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 567)
  - Crowder: The Representation of Speech Sounds in Human Memory, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 568)
  - Scarf: The Adoption of Mentally Retarded Children, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 569)
  - Moore: Effects of Social Norms and Social Approval on Children's Prosocial Behavior, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 570)
  - Fetter: A Computer Environment for Database Access and Analysis, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 571)
  - Diaz: Preadolescent Friendships, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 572)
  - Golding-Mather: The Relationship of Depressive Patterns, Daydreaming Styles, and Sex Roles, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 573)
  - Jensen: Psychobiological Factors in the Prognosis and Treatment of Neoplastic Disorders, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 574)
  - Myers: The Epidemiology Catchment Area Program, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 575)
  - Rodin: Aging: Dietary Habits, Social Factors, Stress, and Health, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 576)
  - Heller: Developmental Changes in the Formation of Impressions about Another Person, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 577)
  - Weaver: Museum Tour Captioning for the Hearing-Impaired, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 578)
  - Tischler: Training Program in Mental Health Services Research and Evaluation, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 579)
  - Marcus: A Reaction Time Study of the Disembodied Eye Phenomenon, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 580)
  - Mauro: Caricature and Face Recognition, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 581)
  - Mauro: Saints, Sinners, and Social Prototypes, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 582)
  - Rodin: Metabolism and Eating Habits, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 583)
  - Hackman, Judith: Senior Profile Study, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 584)
  - Ickinger: Exploratory Study of Human Spatial Behavior in an Unfamiliar Setting, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 585)
  - Peters: Effects of Distraction in Schematic-Based Understanding, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 586)
  - Black: Mental Models and Learning, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 587)
  - Hackman, Richard: The Design and Management of Work Teams, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 588)
  - Veilleux: Attitude change as a Function of the Vividness of the Message Presentation, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 589)
  - Goldfarb: The Relationship between Conceptions of Child hood and Ideas about the Role of the Child's Custodial Preference in Custody Adjudication, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 590)
  - Kristeller: Reduced Environmental Stimulation in the Treatment of Hypertension, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 591)
  - Eisenstat: Job Satisfaction and Burn-out In Human Service Workers, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 592)
  - Felner: An Analysis of Transitional Care Facilities, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 593)
  - Garner: Perception of Structure, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 594)
  - Berndt: Relations of Sibling Interaction to Peer Interaction, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 595)
  - Gonzalez: Determinants of Felt Injustice, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 596)
  - Urban: The Sociology of Transsexualism, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 597)
  - Philips: Above Average Students with low Academic Self-Concepts: Attitudinal and Behaviorail Correlates, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 598)
  - Weaver: Museum Captioning Materials, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 599)
  - Weaver: Fables, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 600)
  - Triana: Cultural Conflicts of Puerto Rican College Students, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 601)
  - Healy: Reading Aloud, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 602)
  - Alderfer: Untitled (Corporate Governance), 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 603)
  - Alderfer: Untitled (Race Relations), 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 604)
  - Singer: TV Viewing and REading: Cognitive and Neuropsychological Implications, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 605)
  - Warrenburg: Behavioral Etiology and Treatment of Hypertension, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 606)
  - Yee: Spatial Concepts and the Developmental Progression of Children's Art, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 607)
  - Weaver: We All Have Tales, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 608)
  - Wheaton: Social and Genetic Factors in Psychiatric Disorder, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 609)
  - Stolwijk, Deluca, Gould: Public Perceptions of Technological Risks, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 610)
  - Stolwijk, DeLuca, Gould: Program to Investigate Public Perceptions of Technological Risks: Phase I, Preparation, continued, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 611)
  - Fetter: Charles S. Wilson Memorial Hospital Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 612)
  - Berndt: The Influence Process in Children's Group Discussions, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 613)
  - Rhodes: Lateralization of sensitivity to vibratory stimuli: A Signal detection analysis, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 614)
  - Schorr: Perceptions, Attitudes and Beliefs About Various Types of Problems and Concerns and Ways of Dealing With These Concerns, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 615)
  - Fetter: Development of Diagnosis Related Groups Using ICD-9-CM Codes, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 616)
  - Spitzer: The Effects of Environmental Factors on Measures of Appetite, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 617)
  - Holston: The Anthropology of Planned Urbanism: The Case of Brasilia, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 618)
  - Piotrkowski: Job Stress and Children's Mental Health: An Ecological Study, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 619)
  - Janis: Effectiveness of Stress Inoculation and Related Interventions on Commitment and Adherence to Difficult Decisions, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 620)
  - Child: Chance Events, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 621)
  - Scarr: Graduate Research Training in Child Psychology, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 622)
  - Hakuta: Bilingualism, Cognitive Flexibility, and Social-Cognitive Skills in Children, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 623)
  - Scarr: Cultural Variation in Socialization Patterns, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 624)
  - Zigler: Immediate and Long-Term Effects of Intervention for Children and Families at Risk. Study 2: A Survey of Teen Parents, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 625)
  - Ellsworth and Janis: Program in Social Psychological Problems, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 626)
  - Grajek: Sibling Relations in the Context of the Family, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 627)
  - Hook: Attributions of Responsibility for Breaking a Promise, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 628)
  - Felner and Farber: Marital Dissolution: Stress and Coping in Children, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 629)
  - Kessen: Followup Observations of Children Normal Weight and Overweight Parents, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 630)
  - Kimberly and Weiss: The Development and Effectiveness Educational Service Centers: Policy in an Interorganizational System, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 631)
  - Primavera: Transitional Life Events and College Students, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 632)
  - Kaye and Sternberg: The Developing Interaction of Levels of Processing, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 633)
  - Berndt: Bargaining in Middle Childhood and Early Adolescence, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 634)
  - Berndt: Aspects of Social Exchange in Children's Friendships, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 635)
  - Hale: Afro-American and Euro-American Foremothers on Childrearing, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 636)
  - Crosby: Relative Deprivation and Working Women, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 637)
  - Rhoads: Biology of Acculturation in the Solomon Islands, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 638)
  - Goodman: Transnational Corporations and Labor Unions in Argentina, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 639)
  - Singer: Effects of Experimentally Induced Waking Dreams on Creative Problem-Solving, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 640)
  - Liberman: Fishery Management and Jurisdictional Conflict, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 641)
  - Scarr: The Evaluation of a Screening, Assessment and Treatment Program, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 642)
  - Nairne: The Formation of Associations in Human Memory, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 643)
  - Bernstein: The Effects of Motivation Expectations and Similarity Type on the Selection of Comparison Others, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 644)
  - Olzak: Families Facing Change: Attitudes of Educated Women, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 645)
  - Gonzalez: The perception of distributive injustice: A study of the cognitive schema for unfair deprivation outcomes, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 646)
  - Levi: Accountability and Aspiration Level Effects in Dynamic Decision Making, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 647)
  - Healy: The Size and Nature of Reading Units, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 648)
  - McNamara: Semantic and Phonological Activation in long Term Memory, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 649)
  - Schwartz: Reading Comprehension, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 650)
  - Shwartz: Visual Information Processing, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 651)
  - Roseman: Responses to Work and Play Situations, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 652)
  - Kristeller: Physiological Reactivity to Food Cues, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 653)
  - Peters: Recall effects of asymmetrical encoding-retrieval modality in learning of verbal material, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 654)
  - Crosby: Continuities in Relative Deprivation Research, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 655)
  - Rodin: Judging the Causes and Consequences of Problematic Events and Afflictions, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 656)
  - Fries: Development of Patient Classifications of Resource Utilization in Long Term Care, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 657)
  - Kinder: An information-progessing analysis of media agenda-setting, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 658)
  - Serafine: The Development of Musical Cognition in Children and Adolescents, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 660)
  - Rosenberg: Erotic Fantasies in College Males. Relationships to General Fantasy, Sexual Behavior, and Childhood Experience, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 661)
  - Ness: Effects of Meditation and Yoga on Patterning of Cognitive and Somatic Anxiety, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 662)
  - O'Brien: The Machiavellian and Moral Reasoning, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 663)
  - Singer: Clinical Psychology: Health and Child/Community, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 664)
  - Neale: Psychophysiological Concomitants of Task Performance under Stress: Driving, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 665)
  - Schorr: Personality Style and Behavior, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 666)
  - Reiss: Social Sciences Research Training: The Sociology of Social Control, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 667)
  - Tischler: Mental Health Services Research Program, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 668)
  - Doob: Rate Information to Consumers, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 669)
  - Algom: Stimulus independent thought as a function of type of instructions and sex of experimenter in a standard single detection experiment periment, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 670)
  - Mauro: Multidimensional Similarity Assymetrics, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 671)
  - Silberstein, Ferdman: Conflicted Decision Making: The Case of Toxic Shock Syndrome, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 672)
  - Harford: Social Distance and the Sick Role, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 673)
  - Harford: Attitudes Toward Persons Assuming the Sick Role, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 674)
  - Ickinger: The effects of selected behaviors and personality characteristics on dyadic and proxemic behavior, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 675)
  - London: A comparison of the effects of activating vs. inhibiting control strategies on perceived self-control, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 676)
  - Smith, Craig: The Mindlessness of Teaching, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 677)
  - Hoblitzelle: Developing a Measure of Shame, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 678)
  - Pinsky: A Study of Memory Process in Hearing Impaired Children, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 679)
  - Tuteur: Automation EEG Classification, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 680)
  - Sternberg: Teaching Intellectual Skills: A Componential Approach, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 681)
  - Garner: Perception of Structure, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 682)
  - Blatt: The Intergenerational Transmission of Abusive Child Rearing Practices, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 683)
  - Galambos: Metalinguistic Awareness in Bilingual Children, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 684)
  - Lustman: Effective Components of Psychological Preparation Mothers Whose Children Are Undergoing Hospitalization, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 685)
  - Schwartz: Stress Management for Hypertension in Work Settings, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 686)
  - Dembo: Research on Work Involvement, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 687)
  - Turk: Stressors and Coping in the Process of Adaptation to Divorce, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 688)
  - Turk: Diabetes Mellitus: Stress, Coping, and Adherence, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 689)
  - Mjyer: Sick Role Occupancy, Degree of Compliance with Treatment Regimens, and Blood Pressure Control, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 690)
  - Rennert: Diabetes Mellitus and Stress, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 691)
  - Warrenburg: Behavioral Factors in the Etiology of Hypertension, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 692)
  - Grinnell: A Developmental Investigation into Children's Awareness of the Comprehension Process, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 693)
  - Ginter: The Affect of After-School Activities on School Performance, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 694)
  - Scarr: Bermuda Evaluation Project, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 695)
  - Goldstein: Role of the Victim in Criminal Prosecution and Related Civil Processes, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 696)
  - Marmor: The National Coal Policy Project: Theories of Representation, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 697)
  - Schwartz: Psychophysiology of Facial Expression and Emotion, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 698)
  - Berndt: Processes and Outcomes of Peer Influence in Childhood and Adolescence, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 699)
  - Piotrkowski: Job Stress and Children's Mental Health: An Ecological Study, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 700)
  - Pinderhughes: Social Class Differences in Children's Humor Appreciation, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 701)
  - Ellsworth and Janis: Program in Social Psychological Prohlems, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 702)
  - Olzak: Marriage, Work, and Family Roles of College Educated Women, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 703)
  - Berman, Jr.: Social Support and Problem Solving Counseling with Divorced Women, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 704)
  - Bohm: Relationship Quality and Health System Use in the Aged, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 705)
  - Rodin: Aging: Dietary Habits, Social Factors, Stress, and Health, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 706)
  - McGuire: Content, Structure, and Functioning of Belief Systerns, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 707)
  - Montanino: The Federal Witness Security Program: Continuities and Discontinuities in Identity and Life Style, 1980-1981 (Box 13A, Folder 708)
  - Singer and Singer: Cognative and Behavioral Differences in Children with Histories of Heavy and Light TV-Viewing, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 709)
  - Alderfer: Changing Race Relations in Management, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 710)
  - Rosekind: A Psychophysiological Measure of Emotion during Sleep: Patterns of Facial EMG, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 711)